Guide to the Joseph R. Lentol papers CBHM.0004
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 2: Other political campaign flyers, 2001-2020
  - [J. Michael Bruhn, Jr.], 2007 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - [Steven Cohn], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - [Andrew Cuomo], 2006 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - [Maritza Davila], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - [Bill de Blasio], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - [Ken Diamondstone], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - [Steve DiBrienza], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - [Martin Malave Dilan], 2002 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - [Kenneth K. Fisher], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - [Forest City Ratner Companies], circa 2006 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - [Kathryn Freed], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - [Jeannette Gadson], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - [John Glasser], 2007 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - [Tom Golisano], 2002 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - [Betsy Gotbaum], 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - [Mark Green], 2001-2009 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - [Alan Hevesi], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - [Charles J. Hynes], 2005 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - [Steve Kaufman], 2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - [Liz Krueger], 2007 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - [Lambda Independent Democrats of Brooklyn], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - [Brad Lander], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - [Stephen Levin], 2009-2013 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - [John Liu], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - [Carolyn Mahoney], 2020 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - [Marty Markowitz], 2001-2009 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - [Rich McNally], 2007 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - [Gifford Miller], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - [Robert Miller], 2006 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - [Scott Murphy], circa 2006 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - [Kristina Naplatarski], 2020 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - [National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League (NARAL) New York State Pro-Choice 2002 Voting Guide] (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - [New York League of Conservation Voters], 2007 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - [Mark G. Peters], 2005 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - [Stephen Pierson], 2013 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - [Bill Reinhardt], 2007 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - [David Reiss], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - [Diana Reyna], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - [Steve Robelotto], 2007 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - [Debi Rose], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - [Nellie Santiago], 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - [Craig A. Seeman], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - [Alex Shannon], 2007 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - [Norman Siegel], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - [Jo Anne Simon], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - [Eliot Spitzer], 2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - [Scott Stringer], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - [Tom Suozzi], 2006 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - [Evan Thies], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - [Ken Thompson], 2013 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - [Peter Vallone], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - [Jimmy Van Bramer], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - [Nydia Velázquez], 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - [Richard Velasquez], 2005 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - [Melissa Mark Viverito], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - [Vote No Campaign], 2007 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - [David Weprin], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - [Jumaane Williams], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - [David Yassky], 2001-2009 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Series 3: Edward S. Lentol papers, 1951-1966
  Biographical note
  Edward S. Lentol was born on December 26, 1909 in Brooklyn, New York. He attended St. John's University Pre-Law School and then Law School. He married Matilda A. Postis and they had three sons, one of whom is Joseph R. Lentol.
  Edward S. Lentol was first elected to the New York State Assembly in 1948, representing the 14th District of Brooklyn. He remained in that position until he was elected to the Senate in 1962, respresenting the 18th District until 1965, 20th District in 1966, and then the 14th District from 1967-1972. He was elected to the New York Supreme Court in 1972 and held that position until his death on December 11, 1981.
  During his life, Edward S. Lentol was president of the Williamsburg Neighborhood Council and Brooklyn Psychiatrics Clinics, Inc.
  Series 3: Edward S. Lentol papers, 1951-1966, includes photographs, news clippings, certificates of election, a 1958 Democratic Campaign Handbook, and memoranda related to Edward S. Lentol's career as New York State Assemblyman and Senator. Many of the news clippings are election results reported in the New York Times or other newspapers.
  These papers do not cover Edward S. Lentol's time on the New York Supreme Court.
  The series is arranged chronologically.
  - [Photographs of Edward Lentol], 1951-1967 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - [Election results], 1954 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - [Williamsburgh Lodge application forms], circa 1955 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - [Party enrollment numbers], 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - [Election results], 1956 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - [Greenpoint Civic Council constitution and by-laws], 1957 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - "Governors of New York," published by Watertown Daily Times, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - [Registered voter numbers], 1958 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - 1958 Democratic Campaign Handbook (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - [Election results], 1958 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - [Assembly Bills - Banks], circa 1960 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - [Assembly Bills - Public Health], circa 1960 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - [Election results], 1960 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - [Democrat registration], 1961 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - [List of voters?], circa 1962 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - [Registered voter list ED 7], circa 1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - [New York State Senate memos], 1962 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - [Election results], 1962 (Box 8, Folder 42, Box 9, Folder 5)
  - [American Legion citation], 1963 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - [State Senator re-election campaign poster], circa 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - [Election results], 1964 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - [World's Fair Subway map], 1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - [New York State Senate election certifications], 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - [Election results], 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Certificates of election, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 7)